# Andre' Nel

Data Analyst

- nel.andre.m.e@gmail.com
- **484)** 849-1071
- **♀** Harleysville, PA
- in linkedin.com/in/amenel

## Education

Master of Science Materials Science and Engineering Stanford University

Master of Business Administration MSE Business Technology Management San Jose State University

Bachelor of Science Physics, Minor in Mathematics California State University-Hayward

## Skills

SQL Data Analysis Python Machine Learning Statistical Modeling Databases

#### Certifications

Prompt Engineering IBM Data Analyst Professional

## **Summary**

Engineer with extensive experience in mechanical, electrical, and software design, capable of taking a product from concept to customer. Proven track record in fast-paced, deadline-driven environments, with strong project management, customer relations, and communication skills.

## Professional Experience

#### Owner

AMENEL Product Development, Harleysville, PA May 2012 - July 2024

- Provided engineering design services and product development.
- Managed customer communications and project management.
- Designed electro-mechanical systems using Fusion 360.

## Mechanical Engineer

IMAC Systems, Inc., Tulleytown, PA October 2015 March 2024

- Worked on general engineering using various CAD packages.
- Designed simulation and troubleshooting.

### Electromechanical Engineer (contract)

FuelCell Energy, Danbury, CT August 2014 - September 2015

- Designed, developed, and documented fuel cell energy products.
- Created CAD models and electrical circuits.

### Senior Mechanical Engineer

Tiger Optics, Warrington, PA December 2012 - April 2014

- Developed products in the area of gas spectroscopy.
- Managed supplier relationships and project management.